<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetadata xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Name>Stationpedia Ascended</Name>
  <Author>FlorpyDorp</Author>
  <Version>0.2.1</Version>
  <Description>This is a Plugin Mod. It requires BepInEx to be installed with the StationeersLaunchPad plugin.
See: https://github.com/StationeersLaunchPad/StationeersLaunchPad

An enhanced Stationpedia experience with comprehensive tooltips, bug fixes, and quality of life improvements. Stationpedia on a new level. Save time searching through the outdated wiki with descriptions right from the game's source code.

Features:
- Enhanced Tooltips: Hover over logic types, slots, memory, modes, and connections to see detailed explanations
- Operational Details: A dedicated section showing advanced device information and tips
- Page Customization: Replace, append, or prepend descriptions to any Stationpedia page via JSON
- Bug Fixes: Fixed scrollbar handle disappearing and window dragging crashes
- Custom Branding: Phoenix logo and orange accent colors

All tooltips and descriptions are customizable via descriptions.json.

Discord: https://discord.gg/stationeers</Description>

  <ChangeLog>v0.2.1: Enhanced search with smart grouping, visual headers, debris filtering
v0.2.0: Public release preparation, conditional compilation
v0.1.3: Fixed PDB symbol format for hot-reload, added code organization
v0.1.2: Major code refactoring into multi-file architecture
v0.1.0: Initial beta with tooltips, operational details, bug fixes</ChangeLog>
  <Tags>
    <Tag>StationeersLaunchPad</Tag>
    <Tag>UI</Tag>
    <Tag>Helper</Tag>
    <Tag>QualityOfLife</Tag>
    <Tag>BugFix</Tag>
  </Tags>
  <InGameDescription><![CDATA[<size=30><color=#ffa500>Stationpedia Ascended</color></size>
<color=#ff0000>This is a Plugin Mod. It requires BepInEx to be installed with the StationeersLaunchPad plugin.</color>
See: https://github.com/StationeersLaunchPad/StationeersLaunchPad

An enhanced Stationpedia experience with comprehensive tooltips, bug fixes, and quality of life improvements.

ChangeLog:

v0.2.1: Enhanced search with smart grouping, visual headers, debris filtering
v0.2.0: Public release preparation, conditional compilation
v0.1.3: Fixed PDB symbol format for hot-reload, added code organization
v0.1.2: Major code refactoring into multi-file architecture
v0.1.0: Initial beta with tooltips, operational details, bug fixes

<color=#ffa500>Features:</color>
- Hover tooltips for logic types, slots, memory, modes, and connections
- Operational Details section for advanced device information
- Page description customization via JSON
- Fixes for scrollbar handle and window dragging bugs
- Custom phoenix branding

All tooltips and descriptions are customizable via descriptions.json.
]]></InGameDescription>
</ModMetadata>
