<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetadata xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Name>Stationpedia Ascended</Name>
  <Author>FlorpyDorp</Author>
  <Version>0.8.0</Version>
  <Description>This is a Plugin Mod. It requires BepInEx to be installed with the StationeersLaunchPad plugin.
See: https://github.com/StationeersLaunchPad/StationeersLaunchPad

An enhanced Stationpedia experience with comprehensive tooltips, in-game notepad, guides, bug fixes, and quality of life improvements. Stationpedia on a new level.

NEW IN 0.8.0:
- Station Notepad: Full note-taking system with folders, rich text, and Stationpedia links
- Survival Manual: Complete beginner's guide from first minutes to advanced systems
- Game Mechanics: Smelting guide and Species Survival guide with data from game code
- Video/Image Support: Embed media directly in Stationpedia pages
- Nested Table of Contents: Multi-level TOC with smooth scrolling

Features:
- Enhanced Tooltips: Hover over logic types, slots, memory, modes, and connections
- Operational Details: Dedicated section showing advanced device information
- In-Game Notepad: Take notes that persist across game sessions (F2 to toggle)
- Comprehensive Guides: Survival, Power, Airlock, AC, and more
- Bug Fixes: Fixed scrollbar handle and window dragging crashes

All tooltips and descriptions are customizable via descriptions.json.

Discord: https://discord.gg/stationeers</Description>

  <ChangeLog>
v0.8.0: Major Feature Release - Station Notepad, Guides, Media Support
- NEW Station Notepad: In-game note-taking with folders, rich text, Stationpedia links
- NEW Survival Manual: Complete beginner's guide (First 5 Minutes to Advanced)
- NEW Game Mechanics: Smelting Guide and Species Survival Guide from game code
- NEW Media Support: Embed videos and images in Stationpedia pages
- NEW Nested TOC: Multi-level table of contents with smooth scrolling
- Vanilla/Ascended Mode: Click header to toggle (easter egg)
- Multiple guides: Power Systems, Airlock, Air Conditioning, Daylight Sensor
v0.3.0: AIMeE documentation, multi-column TOC, new JSON schema features
v0.2.2: Search optimizations, property tooltips, IC10 helpers
v0.2.1: Enhanced search with smart grouping, visual headers, debris filtering
v0.1.x: Initial releases with tooltips, operational details, bug fixes</ChangeLog>
  <WorkshopHandle>3634225688</WorkshopHandle>
  <Tags>
    <Tag>StationeersLaunchPad</Tag>
    <Tag>UI</Tag>
    <Tag>Helper</Tag>
    <Tag>QualityOfLife</Tag>
    <Tag>BugFix</Tag>
  </Tags>
  <InGameDescription><![CDATA[<size=30><color=#ffa500>Stationpedia Ascended</color></size>
<color=#ff0000>This is a Plugin Mod. It requires BepInEx to be installed with the StationeersLaunchPad plugin.</color>
See: https://github.com/StationeersLaunchPad/StationeersLaunchPad

An enhanced Stationpedia experience with in-game notepad, comprehensive guides, tooltips, and quality of life improvements.

<color=#ffa500>What's New in 0.8.0:</color>
- Station Notepad: Take notes in-game! Press F2 to toggle
- Survival Manual: Complete beginner's guide
- Game Mechanics: Smelting & Species guides from game code
- Video/Image Support: Media embedded in pages
- Nested Table of Contents with smooth scrolling

<color=#ffa500>Features:</color>
- Hover tooltips for logic types, slots, memory, modes
- In-game notepad with folders and rich text (F2)
- Comprehensive guides: Survival, Power, Airlock, AC
- Stationpedia links in notes: {LINK:DeviceKey;Text}
- Fixes for scrollbar handle and window dragging bugs
- Click "Stationpedia" header for Ascended mode

All content customizable via descriptions.json.
]]></InGameDescription>
</ModMetadata>
